ANA KAREN DELGADO

613-413-6494 • delgado_anakaren@hotmail.com • <u>LinkedIn</u> Ottawa, Ontario, K1V 9N2 • <u>https://anadelgado96.github.io/</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front End Developer with over 3 years of experience in structuring, maintaining, and implementing responsive websites. Proficient in HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, React.js, Vue.js, WordPress and Magento. Looking for an opportunity to expand my knowledge in React.js.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Nov 2019 - Present

Agile Thought LATAM • Mexico City, Mexico

- Created multiple landing pages and components for Dolce Gusto's e-commerce website in Magento, transforming wireframes to web pages with the use of Bootstrap, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery and HTML5.
- Collaborated with a Back End Developer to integrate a React page in Magento that shows the nearest collection points for their capsule recycling program.
- Assessed UI designs and prototypes for technical feasibility.
- Created multiple countdown timers for marketing campaigns with JavaScript. These timers showed limited time promotions and increased sales significantly.

Web Developer

May 2018 - Jun 2019

(Internship) UNAM-Canada • Gatineau, Québec

- Created an intranet site using WordPress. This site centralizes important information providing fast and easy access to it and makes collaboration easier.
- Administrated and maintained their WordPress website, managing user permissions and roles and using strategies to improve the SEO.
- Provided training to end users and content managers for both websites and created user and system documentation.

EDUCATION

Applied Mathematics and Computing, Bachelor

Jul 2014 - May 2018

National Autonomous University of Mexico (UNAM) • Mexico Graduated Cum Laude

COURSEWORK

Front-End Development with react (Jan 2022)

(The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology - Coursera)

Developed skills in React.js, such as implementing single page applications using various React features including
React components, Reactstrap and React router, creating and validating forms, creating the architecture for a ReactRedux application, using Fetch and the REST API for client-server communication, testing, building, and deploying
React applications.

PROJECTS

Seenapse

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

• Generated the necessary React components for a new feature that allows registered users to get AI generated ideas, with the use of React forms, and components that render the results of a query to the AI API.